For three years you have endured
and survived our training.
You can run for unimaginable
distances and not be short of breath.
Soon you will be ready
to begin the intense
training that we call the Celestial Gate.
But I warn you again, Zeppeli.
If your choice is to continue with these
teachings, you will be sealing your fate.
The time to turn back
is now. You're young.
You can start a new life.
Master Tonperi, read the waves of my life.
Tell me how long I have.
When is this life of mine going to end?
Where does it end?
How does it end?
Why do you want this knowledge?
I believe there is a purpose to my life.
One that I cannot set aside.
I need to know so I can
fulfill that purpose.
If I know how much time I have to accomplish
it, then I can accept the outcome.
I will accept it.
So, let it be done if
that is what you believe.
Know this.
In an ancient chamber
hidden from the light and
reeking of death a child
shall open the way for You
to unchain a young lion
and release him into the
future of his destiny you
will burn your own Wounds,
then freely Will you open your arms
To the cruel death that awaits? you.
Baron Zeppeli, be careful? my friend.
Here I come, Jojo.
To unchain a young lion and release?
him into the future of his destiny.
I love you, I love you.
I just had a heart.
I'm going to make you move on my Pode.
I'm not that you're only a good cuz.
We're the future.
Judge You!
I can't fudge this collar.
Strange.
For some reason,
Tarkus hasn't made a display of his
tricks for fighting in this room.
That worries me.
Come to me, fools.
You think your hormone will do any good?
You little bugs can't lay a finger on
me, no matter how hard you may try!
You afraid to go to soil yourself?
Masterfully played, Baron.
Here we go, how about
this, Tornado Overdrive?
Watch your back!
He's attacking from above? No, Zeppeli!
He's coming from below!
What do you know, you're both right!
I call it Hell Heaven, Snake Kick!
I, I can't breathe, my hormone
won't manifest. Let's do it!
Joe...
Lord Dio, as you ordered,
they're dead, both of them.
This is...
This bloody savagery is unbelievable!
Jonathan!
Even with a broken neck, you have
the poor taste to still be alive?
Allow me to finish you off.
Jo... Jojo!
Lively for only half a man!
Freely I give this...
Freely I give this to you!
My ultimate technique!
Jojo, take it!
Make it yours!
Ultimate Deep Pass Overdrive!
Gun!
Jojo,
I have passed on to you all the hormone
which was mine to control in this life.
Go, dear friend.
Go.
Baron Zeppeli!
A touching display!
But I'm still going to
grind you into red paste!
You can't do this!
What?
He hauled Tarkus off the
ground like a sack of turnips!
It's as if the Baron's hormone
healed his broken neck!
Numskull, you actually think
you can yank that collar open?
You pathetic waste of flesh!
I couldn't pull apart
those steel bands even
with all the power
given to me by Lord Neo!
Oh no!
Tarkus!
Jonathan!
You bug! How's...
Twisted by madness.
Yes, no human feeling.
You gave up your redemption when
you chose to follow Dio, Tarkus.
Look at that, his hormones visible.
His body can barely contain its strength.
The Baron's Hormone joined and
multiplied incredibly with Jonathan's.
There's been nothing like this ever.
Tarkus, you cannot be allowed
to continue. This is clear.
Your evil spirit must be banished.
Your time is done.
Now I'll erase you.
Enough of your blather.
You talk too much.
You'll have to do better than that.
Cairo!
Cairo! Cairo!
Well played!
Berencippoli!
Speak to me.
This is all...
so terribly wrong.
Without you beside me,
without your wisdom and guidance, how
will I make my way through this world?
Jojo, you simply must
pull yourself together.
You've no time to waste now!
You know what lies ahead?
Now go, leave me.
Settle accounts with Dio.
But first of all, you must
destroy the mask separately.
Please don't cry.
No tears.
I am satisfied.
I have lived my destiny.
When I was young, I was
very happily married.
But to pursue the mask,
I left my family behind.
However, I've never
regretted the choice I made.
I accept it completely.
And it's good.
In the end, I can see that
my choice was the right one.
Jojo, you are my deliverance.
Baron Zeppelin
It seems to me that in you I have found
both a best friend and a new family.
Jojo, through you I will live on forever.
My son, Jojo
The 19th century novelist
William Makepeace Thackeray wrote
To love and win is the best thing
To love and lose is the next best
And so it was that Jojo took
up his mentor's life quest,
as well as his spirit.
Farewell, my friend.
Oh, please, sir.
I beg you, please don't bring
no harm to my child. Let him be.
Hmm.
Do I comprehend you?
Let us clarify what you desire.
Voluntarily, you will give yourself to us.
On the condition that
we not touch your child.
Is that accurate?
Yes.
Only don't hurt my boy.
You move me to tears.
Agreed.
You shall have your wish.
I hereby swear that neither I nor any of
my servants will bring harm to your child.
That said, you need to
be aware of one thing.
All my minions, without exception,
willingly gave up their souls for me.
I truly think it would work out far
better if both of you were to join me.
There would be no more worries.
You would both be part of
a new and greater family.
Remember, you promised
not to hurt my child.
Me for him.
So be it then.
Sweet little child.
As promised, we've not harmed the child.
That's something you've
taken care of on your own.
The irony is lost on you.
A pity.
Struth, Jonathan's demeanour is different.
As if the shutters were drawn on his soul.
And the same for me.
Got no time for tears, only anger.
There'll be plenty of time to
cry once we've dealt with Dio.
Oi, Jonathan!
Dio was swarming about, saying he'd
wipe out the town by tomorrow night.
Zombies will multiply, like
rats breeding in a refuse heap.
No telling what's been
going on down there.
Is Wyn Knight's lot alive or United?
My sister, is she all right? Let's see.
Mr. Adams!
Well, Pogo, what are you doing at this
hour of the night wandering the moors?
Please, tell me.
Is everyone alright?
And my sister, is she safe?
You dare to ask?
You mean to say, you really don't know?
She's bloody furious!
When you get home, she's going to lock
you in the barn and turn your hide!
I guess that means she's safe.
Then let's go!
Well, thank you, Mr.
Adams.
A nice young child.
I have a taste for some fresh, warm blood.
He's been turnt.
Keep your wits about you.
You can't escape me with your human speed!
This is no good.
We're too late again.
That is correct.
The village is lost.
The zombies are everywhere.
Oh, no!
Not another one!
I'm known as Dyer.
A kick?
But why is he so slow?
Try this!
The thunder split attack!
Are you madman?
A normal man would pull back,
but instead you went on the offensive
and attacked me with a headbutt.
Wait, please.
Jonathan Joestar, I am human.
I apologize.
You must forgive me.
I just wanted to see how
well Zeppeli had trained you.
What?
Did you say Zeppeli?
You heard correctly.
Zeppeli is a dear old friend of mine.
We have been through many trials
together over the past 20 years.
That is true.
Hello, my name is Straitzo.
Please read this.
It's a letter.
It was written by...
Baron Zeppeli!
We've only just arrived, but he sent
that some time ago, requesting our aid.
He wrote about the stone
mask, where it could be found,
and especially about the man who wears it.
Hm?
Our training master, Tonpetty.
Greetings to you all.
So you're Baron Zeppeli's
teacher, Master Tonpetty.
In the region I call home, our
custom is not to shake hands.
In this way, we greet each other.
Where is he?
Zeppeli should be here now.
I see.
Zeppeli has passed beyond the Vale.
Even if we had arrived earlier, his
fate would still have been the same.
His death is proof that the strength
this Dio wields is devastating.
His wickedness and his power
are quite extraordinary.
How amusing.
I've put this town in my
thrall in but a single night.
I'll be the roundabout The words will make
you out and out I'll
spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through
the sun And in and out the valley
The music dance and sing They make the
children really ring I
spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through
the sun And in and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the
sky And they stand there
One mile over We'll be
there and we'll see you
Ten true summers We'll
be there and laughing too
Twenty-four We'll be there and we'll
see you I'll be there with you!
Run, run, run!
Falaford, it didn't, you fool!
Straightzo's my name.
No mercy.
I will feel no hint of
guilt for your death!
Come, JoJo!